Hello friends, you are
very welcome to the market.  Friends, in this video we will
talk about ICICI LB Quarter 3
results.  Subscribe to the channel.  If you
like it then like the video.
Friends, let's go here to see
what is the update from the company.  So friends, here you
can see that there is no such update in
which there is any news like dividend bonus.   Let us
directly go to the company's quarter 3
balance sheet where the
results have been shown by the company.  So if
you see here, the amount is given in lakhs.
We will talk in crores.  So here the
company earns income in premium by doing ICICI LB.
Wherever you see,
here the company has shown its income in many ways through
premium which you can see.
So we will talk about total income.
What has been the increase in total income this year compared to last year?
Last year the total income of the company
was Rs 5882 crore, which this time has
increased to Rs 6610 crore.  This
total income was around Rs 6582 crore in the last quarter.
If you talk then there has been a
very good change year on year, which has
increased slightly from quarter to quarter in an increasing order, but that
particular improvement is not visible here,
quarter to quarter in the total income.
Now friends, let's talk
about the company's expenses here from last year to
this year, if you see the
total expenses mentioned here, last year
's total expenses were
5197 crores here, whereas this time the company's
expenses are 639 crores, the same expenses were
around 5830 crores in the last quarter.  So here the company is
seeing more expenses than last year,
which is
more than last year.  So if we talk
about profit, then
what comes out in profit after tax, then friends, here the
expenses of the company are also shown here, if we
look at the total expenses of the company, then
these are also being counted in the tax expenses.
So here we go with the final profit of the company.
Where the
results of the company are shown.  So
if we talk about profit for the period, then
friends, the profit that is coming out of the company
here,
last year the profit of the company was
around Rs 724 crores.  This time the profit of the company is Rs
658 crore.  Whereas
in the previous quarter it was around Rs 819 crore.
So year on year, quarter to quarter, the
profit of the company is falling since last year
and is also seen falling quarter to quarter.  Let's
talk about EPS.  Here, if friends
talk about EPS, then last year the EPS
of the company was
around 14.68, whereas this time it is around 13 points.
Which it was with 16 points in the last quarter.
Thank you.  Like and
subscribe.